{
    "id": "22e60de8e0894e3fbc6d7f5dce3e0d15",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. of her success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "confident",
                "confidant"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want any …………………… explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "further",
                "farther",
                "farthest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there ………………… . in the class?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anyone",
                "no one",
                "someone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor …………………. the patients to quit smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "adviced"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He says he is enjoying his …………………… job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter",
                "latest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "All students should have …………………… .. to a good library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "access",
                "axis",
                "excess"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… football, he plays cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Beside",
                "Besides",
                "Till"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A little",
                "Little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is my …………………… brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun …………………… .. in the east.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "raises",
                "rises",
                "races"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}